Schuyler F. Otteson papers, 1938-1971 C290
Indiana University Archives
- Research and writings, 1945-1970 (Box 4)
  - Doctoral Study in Business: Problems and Contrasting Solutions, 1965 (Box 4)
  - International Economics Materials, 1946-ca. 1965 (Box 5)
  - The Macmillan Company, 1964-1970 (Box 5)
  - Marketing: The Firm's Viewpoint (Box 5)
    - 1963-1970 (Box 5)
    - Adoptions, 1964-1965 (Box 5)
    - Permissions File, 1962-1965 (Box 5)
  - Marketing World, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
  - New Dimensions in Marketing Technology (Newsletter) (Box 5)
    - ca. 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - 1969 (Box 5)
  - Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development (OECD) – (Box 5)
    - Report – Application of Market Research for Small and Medium-Sized Firms in Commerce, 1965 (Box 5)
    - State Department Summer Marketing Study in Europe, 1964 (Box 5)
    - State Department Summer Marketing Study in Europe – Notes, Drafts, Presentation, 1964 (Box 5)
  - Pace College – (Box 5)
    - Doctoral Program, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Introductory Material, 1969; (2 folders) (Box 5)
  - Research Possibilities, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
- Talks and papers, 1962-1971 (Box 5)
  - General Electric Company, 1965-1966 (Box 5)
  - Indiana Executive Program (IEP), 1968-1971 (Box 5)
  - Instituto Post-Universitario per lo Studio dell' Organizzazione Aziendale (IPSOA) – Torino, Italia (Box 5)
    - 1962 (Box 5)
    - Notes, 1962 (Box 5)
    - Profile of a Market-Oriented Firm, 1962 (Box 5)
  - The Institute of Marketing Communications- Westinghouse Marketing Seminar (Box 5)
    - 1966 (Box 5)
    - Transcript, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Otteson, Schuyler F. – (Box 5)
    - Some Insights into Customers of Major Appliances and Their Dealers, 1965 (Box 5)
    - When Our Founding Fathers…, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Otteson, Schuyler F. and Malcolm L. Morris –Role of Marketing in the American System, ca. 1965 (Box 5)
  - Papers of the Thomas N. Beckman Symposium on Marketing Productivity: Productivity in Marketing, 1965 (Box 5)
- Conferences, workshops, and seminars, 1966-1970 (Box 5)
  - Audio-Visual Workshop, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - Crisis in Marketing Manpower Seminar (Box 5)
    - Sept. 1 – Sept. 7, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Sept. 15, 1966 – Jan. 1967 (Box 5)
  - General Mills Conference, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Indiana Society of Chicago, 1970 (Box 5)
- Subject files, 1938-1971; undated (Box 5)
  - Appointment Book, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Calendars (Box 5)
    - 1962-June 1964 (Box 5)
    - July 1964-1966 (Box 5)
  - Centro Interamericano de Comercializacion (CICOM), 1968 (Box 5)
  - Curriculum Vitae, 1952-1971 (Box 5)
  - Ecole Supérieure des Sciences Economiqes et Commerciales, 1967-1970 (Box 5)
  - Economic Letter from Dr. Lawrence C. Lockley, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
  - Europe Trip, 1959 (Box 5)
  - Marketing History, 1965 (Box 5)
  - Meloan, Taylor, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
  - Orescanin, Danilo –Providing Managerial Talent in Pakistan, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Ozaeta, Oscar, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Personal File, undated (Box 5)
  - Property Systems, Inc. (Servicemaster), 1970 (Box 5)
  - Retail Lecture Notes, 1941-1947 (Box 5)
  - Robertson, Ross – West European Seminar, 1968 (Box 5)
  - University of Wisconsin class notes - (Box 5)
    - Advanced Banking, 1945 (Box 5)
    - Money and Banking, 1945 (Box 5)
    - Statistics Classes, 1943-1944 (Box 5)
  - Weimer, Arthur M. – photocopy of photograph with Signed Caption, undated (Box 5)
  - Wells, Herman B –Time Article, April 4, 1938 (Box 5)
  - Wortmann, Herman R. – (Box 5)
    - The E.E.C. and the Developing Countries, 1966 (Box 5)
      (In Dutch)
    - Essays on the European Common Market, 1966 (Box 5)
    - Is the Kennedy Round a Giant Step Toward Liberalization?, 1965 (Box 5)